How is the German auto industry doing now? Maybe
как там автопром немецкий сейчас может
you heard that Volkswagen is
вы слышали что Volkswagen да
converting its plant to produce military
перепрофилирует свой завод под военную
armored vehicles?
бронетехнику
I haven't heard. Yes, it's being prepared here. Uh, I don't
Я не слышал Да готовится тут Ээ я не
know how you feel about this, of course,
знаю как вы конечно относитесь к этому
but damn, Germany and Europe are preparing to
но блин Германия и Европа готовятся
fight against Russia. This is brutal.
воевать против России Это жесть
you strapped into a seat or are those
Понял Это вы пристёгнуты к креслу или
suspenders?
это подтяжки такие
This is help. Yeah, I understand. Where are you
это помощь Ага понял Вы откуда
from Yekaterinburg? And you,
из Екатеринбурга А вы
I'm from Krasnodar, but now I live in
я родом из Краснодара но сейчас живу в
Germany.
Германии
Right in Germany. Yes. You've
Прямо в Германии Да
been living for a long time, yes No. I'm 23 years old.
Давно недавно живёте да Нет 23 года
How is the German auto industry doing now? Or is it
Как там автопром немецкий работает или
normal now? Maybe you heard
нормально сейчас сейчас может вы слышали
that Volkswagen is converting its
что Volkswagen да перепрофилирует свой
plant to produce military armored vehicles? I have
завод под военную бронетехнику
n't heard. Yes, it's being prepared here. Uh, I don't know
Я не слышу Да готовится тут Ээ я не знаю
how you feel about this, of course, but
как вы конечно относитесь к этому но
damn, Germany and Europe are preparing to fight
блин Германия и Европа готовятся воевать
against Russia. This is brutal. There's a
против России Это жесть У меня вот
plant not far from me, they make
недалеко вот этот завод то делают днями
armored vehicles and shells day and night. There's just a
и ночами бронетехнику снаряды Там просто
freak, they'll throw a bunch of equipment at
[__] будут бросать куча техники на
our Russian people. They're
убийство наших русских людей
preparing to fight Russia. That's right,
Готовятся воевать с Россией правильно да
yeah, well, with a nuclear power.  they want to fight
Да Ну с ядерной державой хотят повоевать
So look, they were afraid of us I'm
Так они по смотрите у нас боялись Я вот
looking 3 years ago, uh, Scholz, he said something
смотрю 3 года назад ээ Шольц он говорил
like Russia is a nuclear power, we're afraid to
типа Россия ядерная держава мы боимся
even supply Ukraine with weapons of some kind,
даже поставлять Украине оружие какое-то
yeah, and now we've seen that Ukraine
да а сейчас посмотрели что Украина вон
attacked the Kursk region and Russia
напала на Курскую область и Россия
didn't launch a nuclear warhead That's
ядерную боеголовку не запустила Вот и
all That was Putin's big mistake of
всё Это была большая ошибка Путина
course And well, Ukraine Putin said that the
конечно И ну Украина же Путин сказал что
Ukrainian people are our brotherly
украинский народ - это братский наш
people You've heard that, yeah, yeah So now
народ Вы слышали такое да Да Так теперь
look what the Germans have done They've
смотрите что сделали немцы Они
seen that it's possible to fight on the
посмотрели да что можно можно воевать на
territory of the Russian Federation, yeah, and that's it
территории Российской Федерации да и всё
And they're getting ready in full swing Now,
И готовятся полным ходом Теперь они
of course, they'll do it cunningly They'll
конечно они хитро будут делать Они будут
just flood Ukraine with weapons so that
просто заваливать Украину оружием да
our people die They've been doing this for a long time They're doing the same thing
чтобы умирали наши Это они давно делают
now You can't
Они это же делают сейчас Сейчас Ты не
imagine they somehow didn't give enough
представляешь они как-то мало давали У
I had this plant that was
меня вот этот завод стоял
mothballed Yes, it was re-opened before the New
законсервированный Да его ээ перед Новым
Year and now they're just
годом расконсервировали и сейчас просто
firing in three shifts They're firing in three shifts I've
в три смены лупят В три смены лупят Я
already sent its coordinates to the guys I
уже там скидывал его координаты ребятам
know with Nuni, you know, like So,
знакомыми с Нуни там понимаешь типа
damn,
Так так что блин
and on  How do they watch Trump? What's wrong
а на Трампа они как смотрят трамп-то что
with Trump? Trump is bad. Everything is bad.
плохо плохо на Трамп Всё Трампа уже
Nobody likes Trump here anymore. It's
никто не любит тут и
clear.
всё Это понятно
What countries, for me,
Что стран по мне
and for some reason they don't like us Russians either. For
ну и нас что-то русских так не любят Вот
example, me. I've been living here for 23 years. Yes, I've
например меня Я живу тут 23 года да я
been like, What city do you live in? What city do you
уже как бы Вы в каком городе вы в каком
live in? Bavaria. Bavaria.
городе жите бавария Бавария
Munich. In Munich. Bavaria.
Мюнхене В Мюнхене Баварии
Well, I have relatives of my wife who
Ну у меня есть родственники моей супруги
live in Germany normally.
живут в Германии нормально
They've been living there for more than 20 years. The children have already
Они уже живут больше 20 лет дети уже там
studied there and they also live their own lives.
выучились и живут тоже своей жизнью
Well, it's true that they have social housing. For
Ну правда у них социальное жильё Сове
some reason, they haven't bought an owl yet. But I'm the
пока не купили почему-то Но я
only one you know that
единственное вы знаете что вот меня до
still torments me. I haven't lived in Russia for 23 years,
сих пор мучает Я уже 23 года не живу в
but I can't understand. I'm
России да но я не могу понять Вот я
looking at the standard of living in Russia, the standard of
смотрю уровень жизни в России уровень
living in Germany. My mother is still
жизни в Германии У меня ещё мама сейчас
in Krasnodar with my father. How is
осталась в Краснодаре с папой то как
our Russia, having oil, gas, gold, diamonds,
Россия наша имея нефть газ золото алмазы
selling all this gas to Europe, living
продавая весь этот газ Европе да живёт
worse than Europe? Why is that?
хуже чем Европа Почему так
Where do you think she gives the money to Europe?
что думаете она куда деньги в Европу
I just don't know why it
отдаёт что ли я вот вот не знаю почему
turns out that in Germany there is no gold,
получается вот в Германии нет ни золота
diamonds, oil, gas. No, there simply isn't. She
ни алмазов нефти газа Нет просто нет Она
really, really takes and  somehow it makes it so that
реально реально берёт и как-то делает
people have more money than
так чтобы денег было у людей больше чем
in Russia How can I not
в России Как не могу
understand
понять
Yes Well and I do not know how it is in Germany In
Да Ну и не знаю как там в Германии В
Germany, too, people are different, they
Германии тоже люди разные по-разному
live differently, I think Just like in
живут я думаю Как и в
Russia, people
России люди
live differently
живут по-разному
Some work, some do not want to work,
Кто-то работает кто-то не хочет работать
I think So Yeah Well and the fact that the wealth in
я думаю Так Угу Ну а то что богатство в
Russia is all mineral wealth Well, it is not these
России там недрода всё Ну это же не эти
Arab Emirates or wherever, where
не Арабский Эмираты или там куда где у
they have a lot of oil and a small population,
них нефти полно а населения мало
territory And we have
территории А у нас территории
large territories Well, I mean Russia That
большие Ну России я имею в виду То
Russia is poorer than Europe because it has a large
Россия беднее Европы потому что большая
territory, yes Well, no,
территория да
it is not connected with the territory And
Ну нет не связано это с территорией А с
what is it connected with Well,
чем связано
I do not think the
ну я не думаю не намного отличается
standard of living is much different That is how you say it here
уровень жизни Вот вы так это тут
and I do not believe in it, that the
говорите а я в это ну не верю что там
level there is much higher than in Russia Well,
уровень намного выше чем у России Ну
somehow, how is it that in
как-то ну как как получается что в
Germany they can pay salaries 10 times
Германии могут зарплату платить в 10 раз
higher than in Russia
больше чем в России
Well, but in Germany they can probably spend Yes, they can Yes, they
ну зато в Германии наверное и тратить
can But how is it that
могут да могут да могут Но как
Germany can make it so that
получается как Германия может делать так
people receive higher salaries
чтобы люди получали больше зарплату
Well, Germany does not support its army There
ну Германия не содержит свою армию Там
they hid under NATO Well, they
они под НАТО спрятались
also do not spend money on defense
Ну тоже не тратить деньги на оборону
Understood That is all they
Понял То вся получается
will spend now  say Yeah So it
сейчас будут тратить говорите Угу То
turns out they want it already, it turns out that all the
получается хотят уже то получается вся
poverty of our Russia is due to the fact that it
бедность нашей России из-за того что она
spends all the money on the army Yes Well,
тратит все деньги на армию Да
why Well,
Ну почему
my mother My mother in
ну вот у моей мамы у моей мамы в
Krasnodar has a pension of 18,600 rubles
Краснодаре пенсия 18.600 руб
That's 180 euros
Это 180 евро
Well, a pretty good pension in
Ну довольно-таки неплохая пенсия в
Krasnodar
Краснодаре
Well, like in Germany, our homeless people
Ну как бы в Германии у нас бездомные
receive 10 times more benefits
получают в 10 раз больше пособия
That your mother is
Что ваша мама
unhappy with her standard of living Yes, she
недовольна уровнем жизни своим да она
worked for the state for 35 years as a
проработала 35 лет на государство
nurse in a district hospital, of course she is
медсестрой в больнице районной конечно
unhappy Well, it
недовольна
is clear that the pension is
Ну понятно что пенсия
small I agree
это маленькая я соглашусь
but well, people survive And what is
но ну жить люди выживают Причём что
interesting is that scammers steal
интересно у пенсионеров мошенники воруют
millions from pensioners from Russian pensioners where
миллионы у российских пенсионеров где
they are Like Koreika millions are probably
они как у Корейка миллионы наверное
hidden somewhere Yeah Well, the
спрятаны где-то Угу Вот
scammers are from there, from Europe or from where,
мошенники оттуда из Европы или откуда
or from
или из
Ukraine And you, like a patriot of Ukraine,
Украины А вы якжу патриот Украины
right, no Well, you, the yellow-blue
правильно нет А ну вас жёлто-блакитный
background at the back
сзади фон
is the flag of my town near
Э это флаг городка моего воз возле
Munich
Мюнхена
Ulserdorf He also has a flag like that, just
Ульсердорф У него тоже такой флаг просто
like Ukraine
как у Украины
Well, there is a
Да
different coat of arms there  does not trident Why do
ну герб другой там не трезубит Почему у
you have VPN this is Ukraine too and because yes
вас VPN это Украина тоже а потому да
because I installed VPN If I go out
потому что я ставил VPN Если я выхожу
without a VIP I only
без випна у меня только Германия
get Germany because I am in Germany and I
попадается потому что я в Германии а я
put Ukraine And then I get both
ставлю Украину И тогда мне попадаются и
Russians and Ukrainians and it is interesting for me to
русские и украинцы и мне интересно
talk then
разговаривать тогда
Well and I am Russia I just put the
Ну а меня стоит Россия Я просто ставлю
country I want Ukraine I put Here
государство какое хочу Украину ставлю
I put Ukraine and you tell me from
Вот Вот я поставил Украину а вы мне из
Germany: "You [ __ ] like that because
Германии говорите: "Выбли так потому что
yes because I chose Ukraine" And if I
да потому что я выбрал Украину" А если я
choose that I am from Germany then I will
выберу что я из Германии то я буду
get to those who will choose
попадать на тех кто будет выбирать
Germany You see that no
Германию Понимаете то есть ни на кого
one chooses Germany I
никто не выбирает Германию Я вот здесь
was talking here and they have Germany and I
разговаривал и стоит у них Германия и
came across
попадались и
such negotiators people spoke to me
такие переговорщики со мной говорили
And although I mainly put Belarus and
А хотя я в основном ставлю Белоруссию и
Ukraine
Украину
And what do you do
А вы кем работаете
I am a dispatcher
я диспетчер электрический
engaged in electric power supply Understood And by the way, how is it
энергоснабжением занимается Понял А как
now in Russia with medicine
кстати сейчас в России с медициной
because I heard that there it has
потому что я слышал что там вообще очень
become very bad and expensive with medicine yes
плохо и дорого стало с медициной да
pretty good
довольно-таки неплохо
constantly it invites everyone for a medical examination
постоянно это диспансеризацию приглашает
and this and all workers regularly have a medical commission
и это а работников все медкомиссию
pass So how
регулярно проходят Так что сколько
much does it cost now in Yekaterinburg to
сколько сейчас вот у вас в Екатеринбурге
make a normal jaw,
стоит сделать челюсть нормальную
well, they say about ninety thousand here, well, without
ну говорят тысяч девяност тут ну без
implants And I am a veteran of labor, they give me
имплантов А я ветеран труда мне
free dentures It's just that I broke some of my teeth,
бесплатно протезирует Просто я зубы
some of mine broke, some of mine
свои мне часть сломил сломались свои
were broken, and some of these dentures are full
были часть и часть эти протезы полные
dentures And I'm standing there now, I just
протезы И я стою сейчас я их просто
rarely
редко
wear them,
одеваю
but they put me on the waiting list for free
а меня поставили на очередь бесплатно
as a veteran of labor They
как ветерана труда Протезирование
put me on the waiting list for free Well, I
бесплатное на очередь поставили Да ну я
already did it once and I
уже один раз по сделал и мне вот
need this, I say, fix them And after
это надо говорю их подправить А через
how long will the queue be suitable, how long does it
сколько очередь это подойдёт сколько она
last, the queue, well, something like that, the
идёт очередь ну се
queue
что-то очередь
lasts two or three years, they say, yes, but it's
длится года два-три говорят да а
cool Well, that is, quite quickly That
прикольно Ну то есть довольно быстро То
is, it's not a decade, but in 2-3 years you
есть это не десятилетие а за 2-3 года
can still wait And so, And so, since
это ещё можно подождать А так вот А так
I work, I could of course pay
я как работаю я мог бы конечно заплатить
Well, there is such advertising that they
Ну там эти причём реклама такая что
did it pretty quickly They want to do it in 2 days
довольно быстро сделали За 2 дня хотят
Although I don't know, I walked there while
сделать Хотя не знаю я там ходил пока
they were measuring me, they finished measuring
они мне там мерили
these
домерили эти
jaws, well, first they treated my teeth, then they
челюсти это ну сначала зубы лечили потом
measured my jaws It's a process And they
челюсти мерили Это процесс А они быстро
say quickly, well, it's true, they say they can put it on
говорят ну правда говорят могут на
four implants
четырёх имплантах
Well, the prices are like that  in my opinion 90,000
поставить Ну цены такие по-моему 90.000
Well, listen here is also such a question, how is it
Вот А слушай тут тоже такой вопрос как
so, how is your
бы как так ну как у вас организована та
system organized that they will have time to skip the whole queue in 3
система что они успеют всю очередь за 3
years, well, because here in
года пропустить ну потому что у нас в
Germany it is generally unrealistic in 3 years. Here,
Германии вообще нереально за 3 года У
if you make an appointment with a dentist, you
нас если записываются к стоматологу то
have to wait about five years. That is, how is it that
это лет пять надо ждать То есть как у
you organized it so that
вас так получается организовали что
they can process such a flow of people in 3 years,
такой поток людей за 3 года они могут
but this is somehow very fast. Well, the
обработать но это как-то очень быстро Ну
preferential leave, I dont think its big,
льготная отшасть я не думаю что большая
but many even go for paid
но многие даже идут на платное
prosthetics. Well, what is your
протезирование Ну
salary? Your
а зарплата сколько у вас
salary is small. What 80? 80?
зарплата небольшая Какая 80
800 euros
80 800 евро
80,000 Well, 800 euros, yes, its hard. How do you
80.000 Ну 800 евро да тяжело А как вы
survive on this salary?
выживаете на эту зарплату
And what about my milk, which costs 8
а что у меня молоко стоит 8
rubles? Bread is probably 5 rubles there.
руб Хлеб 5 руб наверное там
Well, lard is 700 rubles a kilogram, or whatever
Ну сало 700 руб килограм или что там
bread is there. Bread is 5 rubles. This is some kind of fodder
хлеб Хлеб 5 руб Это какой-то кормовой
bread made from fodder grain, or what is bread for 5 rubles?
хлеб из фуражного зерна или что за 5 руб
No, its bread. This is a loaf with pipes,
хлеб нет это хлеб Это булка со трубями
so expensive. Smak is such a company. Wait a minute.
такая дорогая Смак такая фирма А подожди
what kind of feed bread is 5 rubles It
каковой кормовой хлеб 5 руб Это
turns out shorter than 5 cents bread
получается короче 5 центов хлеб
Yes, it's
Да
cool
прикольно
And white And it's also cheaper
И белый А ещё и дешевле есть
Cheaper cheaper 5 rubles bread
Дешевле дешевле 5 руб хлеб
How not 5 rubles 50 I said five 50 And already
Как не 5 руб 50 Я говорил пять 50 А уже
50 Oh, I got it I was
50 О понял Это я
wrong 50 Well, you know why it's
ошибся 50 Ну это это знаешь почему это
because there aren't enough vitamins in the
потому что витаминов не хватает в
body Poor nutrition causes
организме Слабое питание пропадает
mental abilities to disappear Oh, I understand You're
умственные способности А ну понятно Ты
already starting You need to not I'm serious I'm serious You
уже начинаешь Нужно не Я серьёзно говорю
need to eat I I understood that
Я серьёзно Нужно кушать Я я я понял что
you're serious but give me something else No, not
ты серьёзно но давай ещё меня чем-нибудь
me But I look I was
Не не я А я смотрите я восемьдесят
born in 1981 And what
первого года рождения А вы какого
year were you
какого года я восемьдесят первого года
born I was born in 1981 And you and
рождения А вы
I were born in 1950 1950
а я пятидесятого
So it turns out you'll be
Пятидесятого Так тебе получается тогда
75 this year yes if you were born in
75 лет будет в этом году да если ты
1950 then you should
пятидесятого года то тебе 75 лет должно
be 75 this year 74 Well, it will be five So
быть в этом году 74 Ну будет пять Так а
what are you working and not retired and I
что ты работаешь а не на пенсии а мне
like to work And how much is your
нравится работать А сколько у тебя
pension they have
пенсия
n't indexed me because
меня же не индексировали потому что у
I've been working since 1916 the
меня я с шестнадцатого года я же работаю
state doesn't index me Well,
меня индексацию не проводит государство
you  here Yes yes you are a veteran of labor then
Ну ты вот Да да ты ветеран труда то
how much pension do you have
сколько у тебя пенсии
I was also awarded an order Here with an order
я ещё награждён орденом Вот с орденом
How much pension do you have
Сколько у тебя пенсии
listen you are a blogger yes do you want to
слушай ты блогер да хочешь меня тут
sign me up here but just tell me how
записать а просто скажи сколько пенсия у
much pension do you have you are a veteran of labor there is an order yes
Сколько пенсия у тебя нормальная пенсия
How much is your pension normal decent
достойная Ну сколько представляешь
pension Well how much can you imagine but I will not tell you That is you are a veteran of labor they gave you an order but I am ashamed to say the size of the pension yes Yes I will not get involved I am not ashamed
а размер пенсии стыдно сказать да
of myself because
Мне ничего за себя не стыдно потому что
Yes And that is why I have lived I am already an old
Да И поэтому я прожил Я уже старый
man and you want me this Look and at
человек а ты меня хотишь это Смотри и в
75 you work not because you
75 лет ты работаешь не потому что тебе
want to work but because you will
хочется работать а потому что на твою
not survive on your pension
пенсию не выживешь
Well you see how you look at it yes well
Ну вот видишь ты как на это смотришь да
everything is clear with you Russian you are my
ну всё понятно с тобой русский ты мой
man
человек
My mother also works yes she has 18,600
Моя мама также работает да у неё 18.600
pension
пенсия
and that is why she still works But there
и поэтому она работает до сих пор Но
is And how much does she earn and
есть И сколько зарабатывает м
receive how much 45,000
получает сколько 45.000
Well a normal salary is
Ну нормальная зарплата
450 euros Well that's it yes
450 евро Ну такое
You probably have travel there  in
да У вас же у вас там наверное проезд в
transport it's more expensive to get a haircut probably
транспорте дороже Постричься наверное
expensive Well with
дорого
us yes with us it's expensive to wash You you
Ну у нас да у нас помыться дорого Вы вы
water you water this water water means
воду вы воду это воду воду значит
you wash then toilet this water you
моетесь потом унитаз эту воду экономите
even save on water Well yes yes we have this
на воде даже Ну да да это есть такой у
Look I'll tell you too honestly surcharges are
нас Смотри я тебе тоже честно сюрплаты
big very big Yes But you
то большие очень большие Да Но за жильё
pay more for housing yes but for housing it's
больше платите да но за жильё это жесть
just brutal you know look my salary is
просто понимаешь смотри у меня зарплата
yes 6,000 euros but for housing I pay yes 200
да 6.000 евро но за жильё я плачу да 200
euros This is brutal It's just This is
евро Это жесть Это просто Это по-вашему
20,000 rubles in your opinion This is some kind of rip-off you
20.000 руб Это обдираловка какая-то
know this is a rip-off Moreover water
понимаешь это обдираловка Больше того
I water like this like my mother in
вода Я воду так вот как у меня мама в
Russia she doesn't she turns on the water and it flows With
России она не она открывает воду и течёт
me it's like this If more than that if I
У меня так Если больше того если я
turn on the water it's priced like gold you
открываю воду она ж по цене золото
know it's like
понимаешь она как
Coca-Cola We wash ourselves in the bath well here I have
Кока-Cola Мы как моемся ванне ну вот у
uh I'm a wife and five more children us yes then we bathe it
меня ээ я жена и ещё пятеро детей нас да
turns out I first
то мы купаемся получается я сначала
bathe then she bathes and then
купаюсь потом она купается и потом
bathes the
купает
children in this No no  joke Yeah
детей в этой Да не прикалывайся
seriously do
Да серьёзно
n't joke about me Of course you
не прикалывайся надо мной Вы конечно
save but not to such a wall Expensive
экономите но не до такой стены Дорогая
water what a nightmare We have meters for water for
вода что жесть У нас счётчики на на воду
hot and cold meters So we are not
на горячую на холодную сачётчики Так нас
only not on heating We have a
только на отопления нету На мы там
total of gigacalories there Heating is
гигакалории общей стоит Отопление
expensive and water well what do I never
дорогое а вода ну что никогда не
save on the toilet I don't save
экономлю ни в унитазе не экономлю
anything Well yeah
ничего Ну
And nobody saves Yeah yeah
Угу И никто не экономит
we live badly Bad Well well you
Да да плохо мы живём Плохо Ну
know what the paradox is here in
ну вот знаешь в чём парадокс у нас в
Germany here in Germany all the
Германии у нас в Германии все с хорошими
old people walk around with good teeth But in Russia our
зубами ходят старики А вот в России наши
poor guys Why can't I understand what
бедолаги Почему так не могу понять что
you in Germany and in Russia In Germany in
вас в Германии и в России В Германии в
Germany all the old people walk around with good
Германии все старики ходят с хорошими
teeth but in Russia we have to wait
зубами а в России у нас приходится ждать
three years for a preferential queue Why is it why is it
им у льготную очередь три года Почему
different people some don't
так почему так ну разные люди кто-то не
want to and don't walk and
хочет и не ходит а
some walk You see, you noticed
кто-то ходит Вот вы видишь обратили на
my teeth that I have dentures yeah and you've
мои зубы что у меня протезы да а вы
seen people without a leg with dentures you've seen
людей без ноги видели на протезах видели
In Germany there are such
В Германии есть такие
people Well I have dentures I just
люди Ну а у меня протезы я их просто
take them off They are for me
снимаю Мне
Well, removable, what to chew only But why do I need
они ну съёмные что жевать только А
them
так-то они мне зачем
here, fiction of
тут фикцию
speech, like this Aikin
речи-то как этот Айкин
said, diction, fiction Listen, what do you
говорил дикцию Фикцию Слушайте а как вы
think, Putin, he's old like
считаете вот Путин он же старенький как
you, yes, he'll die soon, yes, who will come
вы да он скоро умрёт да кто вот будет
after him, who is worthy of leading Russia
после него кто достоин возглавить Россию
after him, and are you planning to live forever, or
после него а вы что вечно жить собрались
what, Putin's spring, no Well, Putin will
что ли на Путина весно нет Ну Путин
die soon You all understand this already He's
скоро умрёт Это все уже понимаете Он
old like you Yes, tell me who will be,
старенький как вы Да скажите кто будет
who will be, how long, how long, are you
кто будет сколько через сколько вы его
burying him, soon he will die this year
хороните скоро в этом году умрёт он
We, people live for 90 years Well, they live for 90 years, yes,
Нас люди по 90 живут Вот 90 лет живут да
who will come instead of him, what do you think, Putin the
то кто будет вместо него как вы считаете
second will come Putinka, who will come, well, who will be for the
путин второй придёт Путинка кто будет ну
second Putin, well, that's all Putin 2
кто что за второй Путин ну и всё Путин 2
Well, more specifically,
Ну а конкретнее
well, as a specific person, so to speak,
ну я как конкретный что так сказать
can I say
можно
someone, if it were Zhirinovsky,
кого-то вот был бы Жириновский его бы
I would put him in, You are for
поставил Я бы его поставил Вы за
Zhirinovsky, yes, I
Жириновского да
would put him in Well, I get it Damn, that's
я бы его поставил Ну понял Блин вот это
also such an interesting paradox I'm wondering
тоже такая интересный парадокс Я сю
why everyone in Russia is for Zhirinovsky
почему все в России за Жириновского Вот
Damn, what a paradox  Who is for
блин какой-то парадокс Кто за
Zhirinovsky, well, why in Russia is everyone
Жириновского все ну почему в России все
for Zhirinovsky, why do you
за Жириновского почему так
see that you are starting to behave like this again,
вот видите вы опять начинаете
I would say so Why, well,
вести я бы так сказал Почему ну
because And did you hear that Zhinovsky
потому А вы слышали что Жиновский
called the Uralians, did you hear that, yes Yes, I heard, I heard Yes Well, I heard too I heard too So
уральцев называл слышали такое да Да
what now, yes That is, it
Я тоже слышал Ну и что теперь да То есть
turns out that you are a Uralian, he called you
получается и вы уралец он вас называл
that, and you are
так а вы за
rubbing for him I am not from the Urals, I am from Ukraine,
него трёте Я-то не с Урала я с Украины
so I can No, I am from the Urals You are a
поэтому мне можно Нет я с Урала Ты
Uralian That's all Ekaterina It is I who live here Well, that's
уралец Всё Екатерина Это я тут живу Ну
all you are already speaking in Russian No, but
всё ты уже размовляю на рыдной мове Нет
he, he says that there in Russia,
так он же он же говорит что там в России
yes, there in the Urals, there are magnetic anomalies,
да там на Урале магнитные аномалии там
everyone is becoming Where was I born in
все становятся Откуда я-то родился-то на
Ukraine, so I can Yes, you were
Украине поэтому мне можно Да да ты был
normal, but you came and stayed, these
нормальным но приехал побыл эти
magnetic anomalies and that's it And already A
магнитные аномалии и всё И уже
wow, well,
А вох да
if that's the theory, then yes
ну если так такая теория-то да
Yes, I have a feeling that I was
Да у меня такое ощущение что я с тобой
talking to you, you already
разговаривал уже
understand, you don't have that, you don't have that Tell me for the
понимаешь у тебя нету такого нету Скажи
first time But that was the case I
первый раз А ведь было такое Я я его
remembered him, I was talking to you,
вспомнил с тобой разговаривал
so I  my memory is better than
так что у меня память лучше чем у
yours Okay, let's take a walk in the forest better You're
тебя Ладно давай гуляй лесом лучше Ты
bad Let's
плохо Давай
ruin you Subscribe to my
развалили тебя Підпишись на мій
Instagram I don't know why you are there Why else are
Instagram Я не знаю для чго це тобі Для
you there to marvel at us Ale for
чого ще тобі там дивитись намі але для
you it's an wonder or three clicks Ale you
тебе це одива або три клика Але ти
support me and I'll say: "Wow,
підтримаєш мене и я буду казати: "Вау в
there's a lot of beauty in me"  followers and I will have a
мене там купа фоловерів и в мене буде
great
класний
mood, cool video" Subscribe to my
настро круті видео" Підпишись на мій
Instagram pop Andrey
Instagram попик Андрей
Otak Let me check for you
Отак Давай я тебе чекаю